We're gonna get going. Go ahead, Ryan.
Sorry to you again.
>> You on mute.
>> All right. Can you hear me?
>> Yeah.
>> All right. How's it going, Kron? First
of all, welcome to Las Vegas. Uh, my
question for you is we saw that we saw a
video of you jumping in the pool after
in celebration you getting picked. So,
just take us through that moment when
you got that phone call um saying that
you're a Las Vegas Raider. Uh I was
already planning on that uh pre
predetermined just like before the
draft. So it was more so like something
I already planned just because like the
excitement something to see but also
just momentum built up. So it was really
more so like a relief. So like that was
really that all it took in that very
moment and I was just really happy as
hell.
>> Congratulations on getting picked. This
is Hondao Carpenter on SI. You started
at Arkansas State with Butch Jones and
but you've only been playing five years,
>> which is really a testimony to your your
want to. Let's talk about your upside.
Would you discuss that please?
>> Uh yes, sir. Uh so it's more so just the
upside for as like my ceiling still
being able to grow, still develop, still
learn just like all the pieces that you
would want as a young player. So like
the the peak that you saw far as
Arkansas State and Auburn, it was a very
small piece. Just knowing the mindset
and the person that I am, it's more so
that you going you going to end up
getting 10 times more of that. So they
know they going to get a dog and I'm
willing to put all my foot all 10 toes
down and everything my best foot forward
for as long as I'm a raider.
>> Thank you. Brandy Flores, Ver Nation
Radio 920. Congratulations. The Raiders
are starting a brand new chapter,
sustainability for the future. How
exciting is it for you to be a part of
the beginning stages of this?
>> Uh, it's very exciting. I'm happy to be
a part of it. Uh, that was one of my
best formal interviews, best uh one of
my best 30 top vid uh interviews as
well. So, it was more so just like a a
very uplifting moment just because they
were already on top of my list. So, it
was they immediately like checked the
box off that. So, it's more so I'm just
more ready to put the work in.
>> Hey, you just mentioned uh they were at
the top of your list. Why were they at
the top of your list? Why was that a
team that you were interested in?
>> Uh the people that's in that people
that's in that uh building. Uh you I
felt the uh the family oriented vibes
and it was more so just like still being
about that but also taking care of your
business at the same time. Like long as
you got the good people that's in that
facility and you bringing more of those
good people in that got the same mindset
and the same outcome, it's going to be
it's going to be 10 times more a winning
establishment because we all going to
want to see success and like hold each
other up to a certain standard.
>> A new defensive coordinator uh in Rob
Leonard. He hasn't done that job before,
so everybody's kind of wondering what
exactly his scheme will look like. What
did they talk to you about maybe
potentially what your role could be and
where do you see yourself fitting in at
the NFL level? Uh we'll talk more about
that once I get down there. So it's more
so just uh they know that they know
they're getting a dog at the end of the
day. So we going to end up working as
far as like putting everything forward
and then they tell me what what to do,
exactly how to do it. I'm going to study
and exactly do exactly that.
>> Hey Kron, Sam Warren with Athletic. Um
we talked about you being new to the
sport. We know that you were a
basketball player before you started
playing football. How do you think your
skills and kind of starting with that
sport have helped you develop as a pass
rusher?
>> Uh just far as like the uh I would say
the wiggle and far as like the twitchy
part of my game is definitely it's
definitely one uh that most don't have
but also something that could uh still
also be improving. So it's just more so
just carrying that on to the football
field and being able to be flexible and
also like move the way I move. It's just
uh uh hand in hand for far as like being
on the court.
Hey, uh, the scouting report on you is
is about work ethic. Almost every scout
that's that's looked at you or watched
you said he works so hard, works even
harder when he's not being watched. Uh,
where does that come from and why is
that important to you?
>> Uh, I would definitely say far as
probably my upbringing, just being able
to uh be a part of um a single parent
home and just seeing my mom work. So
like that's that's all I saw. So it was
more so of just taking that over uh not
even not even trying to but it happened
naturally. So like that that always been
a part of uh me. So it's always been
part of like the way I carry myself.
Even like if I'm not getting praised,
I'mma still I'mma still end up showing
up day in and day out. If and the lights
off, I'm I'mma turn the lights on and
I'mma also go work. I'mma put the work
in. So it's more so just like I don't
care who's watching. I don't care who's
talking about me. But long as I put my
work in, long as I feel good about
myself and I know I achieved today as it
was always a check mark.
>> Hey, Kieran Qers here, Raider Nation
Radio 920. Congratulations. What was
your experience like? How important was
it to be there at Auburn at the time
that you were there and then playing
alongside Faulk as well who obviously is
a hell of an edge rusher, too?
>> Uh, it was definitely it was definitely
a moment that I wouldn't take back. Uh,
I know we didn't win as much, but it was
more so of just like their experience.
It was more so the learning and like
being around the SEC culture and just
being able to develop me as like more my
mentally. So, like it was more so that
just being able to be a part of a a
culture to like just far as like trying
to win, but we know we didn't win as
much. So, it's more so like uh carrying
that over to the NFL. So being a part of
a program that's willing to put the work
in, got the good people that's around.
>> Uh my final question for you is just
what how much do you embrace the
opportunity to play alongside Max
Crosby? And I wonder how much how much
have you studied his game until up to
this point?
>> Uh Max he he was definitely he's
definitely one of my favorite player as
far as just like how he attacks the
field, how he uh carries himself. So
like uh I can't lie. I'mma pick I'mma
pick in the ins and out everything about
him. So, it's more so just taking that
apart and just translating that to my
game, training translating that to my
routine and my schedule and just trying
to be the best person uh as well. Just
being able to uh learn from him at a
young age, but also still being able to
uh bypass him at the same time, you
understand? So, like it's more so if I
can't if I can't bypass him, I
definitely want to uh play on alongside
on the on the other edge.
>> Last one. Leaf Edwards, go ahead.
Hello. You've been quoted uh once by
saying that when you step on the field,
you have a a killed or be killed kind of
dog mentality. Uh when when you make a
statement like that, you know, what does
that look like? Where do you have to
take yourself, you know, within your
mentality of how you play the game to
even get to that point?
>> Uh I can't lie. I just don't like
losing. I I don't like I I don't like I
I don't like losing at all. So, like
it's more so of like I would rather I
would rather run my ass back in the
locker room than let you win. So, it's
more so that
>> Awesome. Thanks so much. Really
appreciate you.
>> Have a good night. Thank you.
>> I appreciate y'all. Y'all take care.
>> Yeah, you too.